var questions = [
    {
      //Question 1
      question: "Where are BICEP from?",
      a: "Dublin",
      b: "London",
      c: "Belfast",
      d: "Edinburgh",
      answer: "Belfast"
    },
    {
      //Question 2
      question: "What was BICEPs first album called?",
      a: "Bicep",
      b: "Nova",
      c: "The light",
      d: "Forever",
      answer: "Bicep"
    },
    {
      //Question 3
      question: "What year were BICEP formed?",
      a: "2011",
      b: "2010",
      c: "2006",
      d: "2009",
      answer: "2009"
    },
    {
      //Question 4
      question: "What year did they first perform at the AVA festival",
      a: "2015",
      b: "2018",
      c: "2016",
      d: "2013",
      answer: "2015"
    },
    {
      //Question 5
      question: "What number did Isles peak to on the UK album charts",
      a: "1",
      b: "2",
      c: "3",
      d: "4",
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      //Question 6
      question: "What is the name of BICEP'S online blog",
      a: "Blog about BICEP",
      b: "BICEPs famous blog",
      c: "Feel my Bicep",
      d: "BICEP opinions weekly",
      answer: "Feel my Bicep"
    },
    {
      //Question 7
      question: "How many members are in BICEP",
      a: "2",
      b: "3",
      c: "4",
      d: "5",
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      //Question 8
      question: "Which house music legend(s) re-mixed Vision of Love",
      a: "Joey Beltram",
      b: "Carl Cox",
      c: "Carl Craig",
      d: "Masters at work",
      answer: "Carl Craig"
    },
    {
      //Question 9
      question: "What label are BICEP on",
      a: "Sony",
      b: "Virgin Music",
      c: "Soma",
      d: "Ninja Tune",
      answer: "Ninja Tune"
    },
    {
      //Question 10
      question: "What year did they win the DJ Mag's 'Best of British Breakthrough DJ' award",
      a: "2011",
      b: "2012",
      c: "2013",
      d: "2014",
      answer: "2012"
    }
];